dsources.com 2007-07-21

# Direct Sources Business Directory - business, product manufacturer, import export, wholesale, supplier, trade leads directory information portal, asia | Info | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Dsources.com understands and respects your concerns about privacy. At the same time, we do ask that you provide information about yourself in order for us to understand your needs better and make your experience at Dsources.com more valuable to you. We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information Dsources.com may collect, how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use (the "TCU") posted on the Site, including the provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the TCU. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the TCU.

By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in Malaysia and/or any other country. 

This Privacy Policy explains: 

_1\. What personally identifiable information Dsources.com collects from you, and how Dsources.com uses the information._

Dsources.com collects and stores personal information in several ways at different parts of our Site. This information may include your name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), areas of interest, financial information, User ID, User Password and other self-identifying information. We collect this information in order to provide you with our services more easily, and in a more personalized manner. We may make message boards and discussion forums available to you. If you choose to voluntarily disclose certain information on any such public area of the Site, this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. We urge exercising caution when disclosing information on public message boards or discussion forums. 

Dsources.com also may request certain information using online order forms for products and services. On the order forms, we may collect contact information, financial information, demographic information, method of payment and, if applicable, a credit or debit card number. We may also collect information about you in surveys or for sweepstakes and contests on the Site and information about the searches you perform and the pages you visit on the Site. Dsources.com may also monitor, on an anonymous aggregate basis, patterns of use in connection with emails that it sends out, including which links are clicked on in our email communications, so that we may use such information to better personalize the content of the Site and our mailings for our users. All such information will be protected in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We may also automatically collect your Internet Protocol address to help diagnose problems and for system administration. Dsources.com reserves the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account for use of the Site. 

Dsources.com uses the information collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Information we collect is used to customize your experience at our Site. We also show you content that we think will be interesting to you, and display content according to the preferences you indicate while on our Site. Dsources.com may use your information to send you promotional materials about Dsources.com and its partners. We may also use your information to contact you, if necessary. 

_2\. With whom your information may be shared._

Dsources.com will not sell, rent or barter your personal information other than to its business partners as set forth herein. However, we may from time to time aggregate statistical information regarding our customers, traffic patterns and site usage, or sell our research, which may contain aggregate information. In addition, we may report aggregate information to our advertisers. Such aggregate information will not individually identify any user. 

In order to provide you with co-branded services, and to improve our features, we will sometimes share your information with our partners. 

We reserve the right to disclose any information if such action is necessary (a) to conform to the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process or subpoena served on Dsources.com, (b) to protect and defend the legal rights or property of Dsources.com, the Site, or its users, or (c) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of its users or the general public. We further reserve the right to release any information concerning any user if that user participates (or is reasonably suspected of participating) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution. 

It is possible that Dsources.com, its subsidiaries, its joint ventures, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that Dsources.com would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. Notice of any such event (to the extent it occurs) will be posted on the Dsources.com website, and we will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

_3\. What choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information._

You may occasionally receive information about the products or services you have selected to place on your personal Dsources.com pages, which may include Dsources.com products and services, and the products and services of our partners. Dsources.com believes that these updates are interesting and informative. In the event you are requested to register, you may be given an opportunity to "opt in" to receive mailings from Dsources.com and/or its partners by "checking" a box in the registration form. (For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "partners" includes, in addition to third parties with whom Dsources.com may have co-branding arrangements or some other business relationship or alliance.) If you submit a registration form with the box checked, you thereby consent to being placed on this mailing list. You may subsequently contact us to request to be removed from this list. In every update that we send, we may include an option to discontinue receipt of future updates. Dsources.com reserves the right to limit any registrations on our Site to those who will accept our information and to those who will provide the requested information. 

_4\. What cookies are, and how Dsources.com uses them._

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Dsources.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. All portions of the Site that prompt you to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. No other company has access to cookies placed on your computer by Dsources.com unless you select the option, upon registering with the Site, to share user-information with Dsources.com's partners. We may use cookies technology to reduce the time required for you to submit your requests and for Dsources.com to respond to such requests. Cookies will not be used by us to retrieve any information about you, or from your computer, that you have not voluntarily given to us. Cookies may also be placed on your computer when you link from the Site to our partners' web sites or when you click banner ads provided on our Site. Cookies placed on your computer by third parties by or through the Site, if any, are not the responsibility of Dsources.com and are not subject to the TCU. Please contact the third party placing these cookies to find out what information is collected and how it is used. You can usually edit your browser not to accept cookies, but the features of our Site may not function properly if you do not accept cookies. 

_5\. How Dsources.com protects your personal information._

For all our transactions, we employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. Where appropriate, we password protect, use encryption techniques and install firewalls. We strive to protect you. We encourage our participating service providers to adopt and honor their own consumer privacy policies. For all our efforts to safeguard your privacy, no system can be guaranteed. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, or that we transmit to you, or guarantee that it will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Once we receive your information, we use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

_6\. How you can access, update or delete your information._

As part of your use of the Site, you are responsible for maintaining and updating, as applicable, your account Registration Data with current, accurate and complete information. You may view, update and/or edit the Registration Data you have provided to Dsources.com by logging in to your account and following the appropriate instructions. 

_7\. What else you should know about your online privacy._

The Site may also contain links to other web sites and advertising. The privacy policies of those web sites and advertisers may significantly differ from that of our Site. It is your responsibility to contact such web site operator or advertiser directly to determine their privacy policy. 

_8\. How you can contact us._

Any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site should be directed to:   
Customer Service  
Dsources.com (GD Net Sdn Bhd)  
B-9-10, Level 11, Menara Uncang Emas,  
Jalan Loke Yew,  
55200 Kuala Lumpur,  
Malaysia.
